ACTWU's National Textile Recruitment and Training Program Records 5619/034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's National Textile Recruitment and Training Program Records
1975-1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union
5619/034
16 cubic feet
16 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, newspaper clippings, and files from the National Textile Recruitment and Training Program (NTRTP) of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union.
6826769
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
February 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 2011
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America And all other 5619 collections.
Textile industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Textile Workers Union of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6826769
- Local 406-T, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Local 508, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Local 21, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Local 35, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Local 66, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Local 1259, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Local 184-T, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Local 210, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local 1057, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Local 1095-T, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Local 1126-T, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Local 1161-T, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Local 1198, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Local 1254, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Local 1256, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Local 1267, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Local 1305, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Local 1307, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Local 710-T, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Local 1374, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Local 1418, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Local 1495, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Local 1550, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Local 1567, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Local 254-T, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Local 307-T, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Local 318, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Local 346, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Local 1766, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Local 1781, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Local 1782 [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Local 1782 [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Local 1808, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Local 1812, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Local 1861, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Local 1846, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Local 1878, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Local 1890, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Local 1920, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Local 1921, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Local 1932, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Local 1944, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Local 2052, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Local 2247, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Local 2352, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Anomatic Corporation, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Central Massachusetts Joint Board, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Greater Toronto Joint Board, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Munsingwear Strike, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Local Organization Drive, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Twin City Joint Board, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Local 1686, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Local 1580, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Local 1586, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Local 1656, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Local 1665, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Local 1666, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Local 1929, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Local 1932, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Training Contract Publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Avon Knitting Mills [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Avon Knitting Mills [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Avtex, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Bemis Co. Memphis Area- Joint Board, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Bemis Intakes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Blue Bird Fabrics Corp., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Bluebird Carryover, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Cosentino, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Cosentino, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Fashion Prints, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Futura Fabrics [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Futura Fabrics [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- J. Bass [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- J. Bass [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Bemis Cotton Mills, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Carmel Weaving, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Everlow Fabrics, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Lehigh Valley, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Lehigh Valley, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Phillips Synthetic Fibers, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Ronitex, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Kalkstein, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Gurney Manufacturing, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Gurney Manufacturing, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Central Alabama-Georgia Joint Board, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Central Alabama-Georgia Joint Board, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Central Alabama-Georgia Joint Board, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- GTA Joint Board Financial Folder, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Avtex Corporation, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Local 7 Nitro Financial Folder, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Memphis Joint Board, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Memphis Area Joint Board Financial Folder, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Zamax, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Zamax, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Pennsylvania-Keystone Fashion Prints, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Pennsylvania-Keystone Joint Board Finance, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Garden Spot Joint Board (Misc.), 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- New Bedford Joint Board, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Chicago Joint Board, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Local 2052- John Santore Union City, NJ, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Memphis Area - Joint Board Nylon Net Co., 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Tennessee Nylon Net, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- New York Metro Scalamandre Silks, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Scalamandre, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Local 7587 Patterson, New Jersey, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Passaic-Bergen Joint Board Kalkstein Silk Mills, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Passaic-Bergen Joint Board Ronitex Fabrics, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Passaic-Bergen Joint Board (Misc.), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Everlon Fabrics Corporation, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Masland, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Synthetic Thread [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Synthetic Thread [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Jonathan Temple [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Jonathan Temple [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Social Service Cases, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Passaic-Bergen Joint Board, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Essex Manufacturing, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Capitol Knitting Mills Co., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania-Keystone Fab Knit Mills [folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania-Keystone Fair Tex Mills [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Nylon Net, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Ruttenberg Joe Kilgallon, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- NTRTP Short Proposal Sub-Contract and Instructional Modules, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- NTRTP Correspondence, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Geoffrey Bauman Book Orders, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Geoffrey Bauman General, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Geoffrey Bauman's Correspondence, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- NTRTP Classroom Program, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Total Completions Column, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Total Participants Column B, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Control Sheet Final, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Final Report, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Control Sheet, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Total Terminations Column C, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Total Participants Column B, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Quarterly Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Total Completions Column D, E, FG, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Total Participants Column B, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Control Sheet, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Total Terminations Column C, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Total Completions Column DEF, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Quarterly Reports, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Close-out 99-7-672-92-14, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Modification, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Graph Sheets, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Reports Quarterly Summary, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Quarterly Report, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  Scope and Contents
  12-30-78
- Total Terminations Column C, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  12-30-1978
- Total Completions Column DEF, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Control Sheet, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Total Participants Column B, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Quarterly Report, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  12/30/1978
- Reports, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  12/30/1977
- QSPC- Final Characteristics, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Graph Sheets, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  12/31/1977
- September Quarter, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Completions Column DEF, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  9-30-1978
- Control Sheet, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Total Participants Column B, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Total Terminations Column C, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- ACTWU Documents, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Reports P.E., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  3/31/1977
- QSPC Final, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Reports P.E., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  4/30/1977
- QSP Final Characteristics, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Graph Sheets, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Reports, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  9/30/1977
- Graph Sheets, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- QSP Characteristics, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Reports, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  6/30/1977
- Quarterly Reports Contract No. 99-6-672-92-11, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Column Sheet Wages, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Column Sheet Male, Female, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- QSPC, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- PSS, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- NTRTP Program. Contracts Proposal & Related Correspondence, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Craftex Mills, Inc., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Craftex Mills, Inc. Philadelphia, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Craftex Mills, Inc. Auburn, PA, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Craftex Status Reports, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Craftex Mills, Inc. Intakes, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Craddock-Terry, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Quilting, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Quilting, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Quiting, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Quilting, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Brooklyn Quilting Intakes, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Chromatex, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Chromatex Intakes, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Chromatex-Allentown Quarter Ending, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Bemis 1, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Bemis September Quarter, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Bemis, TN, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bemis Intakes, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Ballet Fabrics, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Ballet Fabrics, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Ballet Fabrics, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- J. Bass, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Meadville, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Avtex Nitro, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Avtex Aston, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- J. Bass, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Avtex Fibers, Inc., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Avtex Fabrics, Inc. Bills to be Processed, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Carmel, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Avon Knitting Mills Sub-Contract, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Lehigh Valley Throwing, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Everlon Sub-Contract, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Futura, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Fairtex, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Chromatex, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- J. Bass, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Teshon, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Ronitex [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Ronitex [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- J. Temple, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Union Plastics Corp., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Zamax, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- RJR Archer, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Beattie Rug, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Bluebird, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Brooklyn Quilting, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Scalamandre, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Holston Mfg., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Cordova, Inc. Alabama, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Gurney, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Bemis Co., Houston, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Bemis, Jackson, Tn, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Contracts, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Joyce Cotton, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- England, Diana K., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Dorothy Lanham, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Carol S. Poole, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Gwendolyn Ramsey, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Edith R. Smith, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Donzella M. Medcalf, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Dorothy L. Doss, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Rosalie Coronado, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Cordova Spinning, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- C. Cosentino, Inc., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Cordova Mills, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Dec. Quarter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- March Quarter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Cordova Spinning Mills Travel, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Completions Quarter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Terminations Quarter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Cordova Spinning Travel, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Cordova Spinning, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Cordova Spinning, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Ouachita Finishing Co. Monroe, La, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- DHJ Status of Training Report, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- DHJ Monroe, La, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- DHJ, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Ouachita Finishing- DHJ Monroe, La Local 1858, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Downs Carpet Co., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Everlon Closter, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Everlon-Breakdown Travel, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Everlon Quarter, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Everlon Closter [folder 1 of 3], 1978 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Everlon Closter [folder 2 of 3], 1978 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Everlon Closter [folder 3 of 3], 1978 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Eddington Thread Intakes, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Eddington Thread Mfg., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- B&B Dye, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Eddington Thread, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Plus Marks, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Plus Marks, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Poly Cast, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Design Works Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Beattie Rug Contract Rate, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Gurney Mfg. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Gurney Mfg. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Gurney Mfg., 1979 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Holston Hosiery, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Holston Hosiery Intakes, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Holstein Hosiery, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Fairtex Mills Intakes, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Fairtex Mills, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Fairtex Mills, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Kalkstein, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Kalkstein Dec. Quarter, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Kalkstein, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Kalkstein Sept. Quarter, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Scalamandre, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Scalamandre, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Jomac, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Native Textile, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Fibre Yarns, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- St. Charles Furniture Co. Wright City, Mo., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- St. Charles Furniture Corp., 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- St. Charles Furniture Corp., 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Glenmore Plastics, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Glenmore Plastics Trainees from Supplement, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Glenmore Plastics Travel, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Glenmore Plastics Dec. Quarter, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Glenmore Plastics Sept. Quarter, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Glenmore Plastics, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Glenmore Correspondence, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Glenmore Plastics, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Philadelphia Felt Co., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Percy Kent Bag Company, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Jefferies Processors, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Johnathan Temple, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Johnathan Temple Advance Thread, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Synthetic Thread [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Synthetic Thread [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Lehigh Valley Throwing Mills, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Lehigh Valley Throwing, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Royal Yarn, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Zamax Inc., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Zamax Travel, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- 99-7-672-92-14 2nd Contract, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- 99-7-672-92-14 2nd Contract, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Internal Reports, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Midwest Conference, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  May 19-22
- National Endowment Humanities, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Expenditures, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Charlie Twbilla, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Billy Williams/ June Roach, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Gerald Brown/ Lillian Dalton, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Jake Mathis/ Merle Charles, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Memphis, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Carmella DeVita/ Jim Dillon, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Knoxville, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Joe Kilgallon, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Jim Clark, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Human Resources Development Institute, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Synthetic Fibers Division, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- NTRTP, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Budget NTRTP, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Forms NTRTP, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Budget Billing Procedures, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Education Dept., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Congressional District Committees, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Misc. NTRTP, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Educational Reading, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Wisconsin State Historical Society, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Kent Roberts, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Geoffrey Bauman Requests, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Southeastern Massachusetts University, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- R.J. Archer, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Avon Knitting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Avon Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Avon, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Avtex Front Royal, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Avtex Nitro, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Avtex Meadville, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Avtex Lewistown, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Synthetic Fibers & Film Division (Bruce Dunton) Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- J. Bass & Co. Pennsylvania- Keystone Joint Board, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- J. Bass & Co. Pennsylvania- Keystone Joint Board [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- J. Bass & Co. Pennsylvania- Keystone Joint Board [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Bluebird, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- J. Bass (Travel), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Beattie Rug, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Beattie Rug, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Brooklyn Quilting, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Brooklyn Quilting (Travel), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Bemis April Quarter, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Bemis March Quarter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Bemis December Quarter, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Bemis June Quarter, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Bemis September Quarter, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Bemis Graph Sheets, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Bemis Close Out, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Bemis Sub-Contract Background, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Bemis, TN, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Bemis Progress Reports, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Modification Contract, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Bemis Houston, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Bemis Communications, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Carmel Weaving, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Carmel Communications, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Cosentino, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Chromatex March Quarter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Chromatex, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Chromatex [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Chromatex [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Intakes and Follow-Up Forms, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Cordova, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Cordova Blue, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Everlon, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Everlon, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Fairtex Mills, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Fairtex Mills Sub-Contract, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Fashion Print, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Gurney Final, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Gurney Status of Training Report, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Gurney Coordinator Activity Report, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Gurney Sub-Contract Background Proposal, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Gurney Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Gurney June Quarter Intakes, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- December Quarter Intakes, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- March Quarter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Gurney Communications, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Futura Fabrics Corporation, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Holston Hosiery GTA Joint Board, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Lehigh Valley Throwing, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Pennsylvania-Keystone Joint Board, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Nylon Net, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Ronitex, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Scalamandre (blue), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Scalamandre/ Gaff Textile, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Strauss Knitting, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Westchester Lace, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Southern Regional Director Scott Hoyman, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Jonathon Temple, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Inactive Intakes, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Chicago Tent, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Doerr Electric, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Estee Bedding Chicago, Ill., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- United Felt Co. Chicago, Ill., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Columbia Mattress Chicago, Ill., 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Union Plastics Corp., 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Twin Cities Joint Board, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Allstate Lawn Products Twin Cities Joint Board, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Kalkstein, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Ilikon Corporation, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Bemis Terre Haute Industries Indiana Kentucky Joint Board, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Gold Mills Penn. Dye, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Gold Mills, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Midwest Handbag, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Central & South Jersey Joint Board, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Zamax Mfg. Company, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Carmella DeVita North Jersey Joint Board, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Jim Dillon North Jersey Joint Board, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Pennsylvania-Keystone Joint Board (Jack Coury), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Contract 1 99-6-672-92-11, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Payroll Correspondence, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- NTRTP Tender Ellen Agree, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Worksheets, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Contract 2 99-7-672-92-14, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Contract 99-7-672-92-14, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Teacher Peter Agree NYC SS, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Teacher Manuel Aguiar New Bedford, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Catherine Armistead NTRTP, ESL Teacher, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Charles Brennan (Teacher), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Karen Fine (Teacher), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Teacher Nhu-Lang Fowler Resume Williamsburg, Va., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Joan Howland S. Dartmouth, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Teacher Kathleen B. Lund Mass., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Phong Q. Ngo (Teacher) Texas, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Teacher Joseph T. O'Neill New Bedford, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Teacher Ana Roca Florida, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Iris Rosenberg Teacher, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Louis Santiago Teacher, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- John Santos Teacher Fall River, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Teacher Sue Lee Yeungsook Newport News, Va., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 48)